visualphotos.com 2016-12-03

# Privacy Policy | Stock Photos | Royalty Free | Royalty Free Photos

We respect your privacy. Below are some guidelines for your privacy while using this site.

Children

Children (persons under the age of 18) are not eligible to use this website unsupervised and we ask that children do not register or submit any personal information to us. By submitting any information to us you warrant that you are 18 years of age or older.

Personal Information

In order to view images or place an order, it's necessary for us to collects certain personal information from you. We need your email address, shipping and billing address, and other details in order to serve you and protect ourselves against illegal usage. We may also check your credit card number and other information for business reasons such as credit checks. We shall use this information strictly for internal purposes. We won't give this information to anyone else unless required to do so by a law enforcement authority or in cases where we believe, in good faith, that such information is required for non commercial exploitation.

While using this site, we collect information in order to generate statistics for internal purposes. This data shall be treated as business data and we will share it with other parties. However, we won't disclose any personal information in the process. For example, the data will be limited to numbers (i.e. return visits, buying patterns, etc) and geographical locations which will not make it possible to identify you as an individual.

Referral

If you use our referral service for informing a friend about our site, or inviting a friend to view your lightbox, we will automatically send your friend a one-time email inviting him or her to visit the site. If your friend chooses not to visit this site we won't send reminders.

Collected Information

Like most websites, we gather certain information automatically. We shall monitor IP addresses, browser type, screen resolutions, geographical location, entry points, etc. This data doesn't identify you and is used to help us improve the site.

Security

We use SSL encryption and third party technologies to process sensitive information such as your credit card number. While we take the necessary steps to protect your information, we can't protect the data completely against illegal breaking or hacking into our systems.

Cookies

When you visit our website, we send your computer a cookie, which is a small file that resides on your computer's hard drive and contains non-personally identifiable information about the user. Cookies only identify the user's computer as an ID. It does not tell us anything else about you or your computer except that a certain ID has joined the site. Cookies allow this site not to "lose" you while you surf or return to our site. For example, we will send your computer a cookie to maintain your preferred settings such as your lightbox. Not accepting cookies may prevent you from accessing all of the features of the website.

Links

Please be aware that the site may contain links to other sites that do not subscribe to our Privacy Policy. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of other sites and we encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site. Please look for the privacy statements of every website that asks for your personal information.
